A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Publications FA767
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation publications, 1936-2010; 1
  - Ford Foundation Project Status Report, 1952 May (Box 17, Folder 166)
    Includes lists of active, deferred, and dead Ford Foundation Project files. See also the Ford Foundation's Project files (FA733), and the Ford Foundation's Central Index cards, Series 5: Master Cards, Subseries: Projects (FA736).
  - Ford Foundation Project Status Report, 1952 June (Box 17, Folder 167)
  - Ford Foundation Project Status Report, 1952 July (Box 18, Folder 168)
  - Ford Foundation Project Status Report, 1952 August (Box 18, Folder 169)
  - Ford Foundation Project Status Report, 1952 September (Box 18, Folder 170)
  - Ford Foundation Project Status Report, 1952 October (Box 18, Folder 171)
  - Ford Foundation Project Status Report, 1953 January (Box 18, Folder 172)
  - Ford Foundation Project Status Report, 1953 April (Box 18, Folder 173)
  - Ford Foundation Project Status Report, 1953 July (Box 18, Folder 174)
  - Frank Bowles - Various articles, essays, publications, 1960s (Box 18, Folder 175)
  - McGeorge Bundy - Various articles, essays, publications, 1960s-1970s (Box 18, Folder 176)
    Includes "In Memoriam, Kermit Gordon?", Bibliography of McGeorge Bundy publications, "In Praise of Candor", "To Cap the Volcano", "Were Those The Days?", "The Presidency and the Peace", "The Art of Giving", "The End of Either/Or", "The Blessing that is Federal Aid", "Serving the Earth", "The Moral and Social Responsibilities of the Trustees of Foundations", "Faculty Power".
  - Robert Schrank - Various articles, essays, publications, 1970s-1980s (Box 18, Folder 177)
    Includes "Two women, three men on a raft", in the "Harvard Business Review" (1975 May-June); "First, Get Good Data on Youth Joblessness" (1980); "For a Worker-Exchange Program" (1973); "Are unions an anachronism?", in the "Harvard Business Review (1979); "Worker morale: Are there solutions abroad?" (1979); "Horse-collar, blue-collar blues", in the Harvard Business Review (1981 May-June).
  - Francis X. Sutton - Various articles, essays, publications, 1960s-1980s (Box 18, Folder 178)
  - F. Champion Ward - Various articles, essays, publications, 1960s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 179)
  - Kalman H. Silvert and Frieda M. Silvert, "Fate, Chance, and Faith: Some Ideas Suggested by a Recent Trip to Cuba", 1974 (Box 19, Folder 180)
  - Guide to [Ford Foundation] Office Procedures, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 181)
    Includes four parts: 1. Organization [of the Ford Foundation], 2. Ford Foundation Office Procedures, 3. Ford Foundation Defenition of Terms, 4. Ford Foundation Secretarial Techniques and Skills.
  - The Pay of Professors: A Report on the Ford Foundation Grants for College-Teacher Salaries, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 182)
  - The Ford Foundation in Russia, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 183)
  - Grass-Roots Environmentalists: A Report on Ford Foundation Assistance to Municipal Conservation Commissions, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 184)
  - The Good Seed, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 185)
  - The Very Small College: A Report to the Ford Foundation, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 186)
  - The New Teacher: A Report on Ford Foundation Assistance for New Patterns in the Education of Teachers, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 187)
  - A Survey of Black American Doctorates, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 188)
  - Time, Talent, and Teachers, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 189)
  - A Quest for Better Contraception: The Ford Foundation's Contribution to Reproductive Science and Contraceptive Development 1959-1953, by Roy Hertz, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 190)
  - That Our Children Will Not Die, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 191)
  - The United Nations and the Iran - Iraq War: A Ford Foundation Conference Report, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 192)
  - Building Rural Assets: The Rural Development and Community Foundations Initiative (RDCFI) (Box 19, Folder 193)
  - A Foundation Returns to School: Strategies for Improving Public Education, by Janice Petrovich, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 194)
  - Television and Children: Priorities for Research, Report of a Conference at Reston, Virginia, 1975 November 5-7 (Box 19, Folder 195)
  - Ford Foundation Resources for Public Information: A Directory of Selected Headquarters Staff, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 196)
  - The Business of the Arts, Monograph Series, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 197)
    Includes "Linking mission and money: A introduction to nonprofit capitalization", "The people are the message: A museum where contributors are part of the collection", and "Capital structure counts: The business roots of capacity and mission at nonprofits".
  - Ford Foundation, Strengthening Fragile Families Initiative, 1999 Summer (Box 19, Folder 198)
  - The Ford Foundation in Mexico and Central America, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 199)
  - The Ford Foundation and Pakistan: A Ford Foundation Pictorial Report, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 200)
  - Exploring Energy Choices: A Preliminary Report - Energy Policy Project of the Ford Foundation, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 201)
    See also Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (07290125), PA72-125.
  - Sexuality and Reproductive Health: Strategies for Programming, 2001 January (Box 20, Folder 202)
  - Roots of Change: The Ford Foundation in India, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 203)
  - Minding the Children: Ford Foundation Assistance to Child Care Programs, 1980 March (Box 20, Folder 204)
  - Working Against Hunger: Ford Foundation Grants in Agriculture, 1978 February (Box 20, Folder 205)
  - Mental Health: A Ford Foundation Report, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 206)
  - Metropolis, 1959; 1963 (Box 20, Folder 207)
  - The Newsman's Scope, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 208)
  - Ford Foundation 1971 Upper Division Scholarship Competition: Directory of Awards and Honorable Mention Citations (Box 20, Folder 209)
  - International Programs of the Ford Foundation, 1973 July (Box 20, Folder 210)
  - Two African Patterns, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 211)
  - Tapestry for Tomorrow, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 212)
  - Golden Years?, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 213)
  - You're on your way: An orientation booklet for Indochinese refugees destined for resettlement in the United States, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 214)
  - Q and A on Agriculture, Science, and the Developing World: A Briefing on International Agricultural Research and Training Centers supported by the Rockefeller Foundation and the Ford Foundation, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 215)
  - The Ford Foundation at a Glance, Chinese edition, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 216)
  - Ford Foundation: West Africa, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 217)
  - Ford Foundation: Eastern Africa, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 218)
  - African Universities: Stories of Change - The Partnership for Higher Education in Africa, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 219)
  - The Ford Foundation in Brazil (A Fundacao ford no Brasil), 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 220)
  - Men and Women at Home and in the Workplace: Current Debates, Future Directions, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 221)
    Includes material by Charles Brumfield, Arlie Hochschild, Rhona Rapoport, Beth Salerno, and Faith Wohl.
  - The Ford Foundation and Foundation-Supported Activities in India, 1955 January (Box 20, Folder 222)
  - The Utilization of Research for Development, Two Case Studies in Rural Modernization and Agriculture in Peru (Dissertation, Princeton University), by James R. Himes, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 223)
  - Family Planning through Clinics: Report of a Survey of Family Planning Clinics in Greater Bombay, by Dr. Katherine Kuder and C. Chandrasekaran, Demographic Training and Research Centre, Bombay, 1963; Kuder, Katherine (Box 21, Folder 224)
  - Family Planning through Clinics: Report of a Survey of Family Planning Clinics in Greater Bombay, by Dr. Katherine Kuder and C. Chandrasekaran, Demographic Training and Research Centre, Bombay, 1965; Kuder, Katherine (Box 21, Folder 225)
  - About the Ford Foundation, 1955-1972 (Box 22, Folder 226)
  - Current Interests of the Ford Foundation, 1974-2005 (Box 22, Folder 227)
  - Ford Foundation Publications and Films, 1977-1993 (Box 22, Folder 228)
    Bibliography of Ford Foundation publications, films, and videos available to the public. Various editions, issued periodically. Alternate title: "Catalog of Publications, Films, and Videos".
  - Final Report on the Ford Foundation Program for Refugees, Primarily in Europe, 1958 July (Box 22, Folder 229)
  - "To Protect and Enrich the Future: The Ford Foundation, 1936-1956", Joe Jones, Second Draft, 1956 March 29 (Box 22, Folder 230)
  - The Ford Foundation and Indian Economics, John P. Lewis, New Delhi Field Office, 1975 December (Box 22, Folder 231)
  - The Ford Foundation, Travel and Study Awards, Office of the Secretary, 1958 January - 1963 December (Box 23, Folder 232)
  - Directory of Ford Foundation Fellows in Reproductive Biology, 1960-1972 (Box 23, Folder 233)
  - The Ford Foundation, Directory of Foreign Area Training Fellows,1952-1959, 1960 September (Box 23, Folder 234)
  - Papers on Research about Learning: Better Testing, Better Writing: A Report to the Ford Foundation, James D. Atwater, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 235)
  - Affordable Housing: The Years Ahead, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 236)
    A Program Paper of the Ford Foundation.
  - Refugees and Migrants: Problems and Program Responses, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 237)
    A working paper from the Ford Foundation. "A look at the causes and consequences of today's major international population flows, and the Ford Foundation's new programs to address the problems of refugees and migrants in the United States and elsewhere in the world".
  - Community Development Corporations: A Strategy for Depressed Urban and Rural Areas, 1973 May (Box 23, Folder 238)
    A Ford Foundation Policy Paper.
  - A Foundation Goes to School: the Ford Foundation Comprehensive School Improvement Program, 1960-1970, 1972 November (Box 23, Folder 239)
  - The Ford Foundation's Work in Population, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 240)
    A working paper from the Ford Foundation. "A review of past and present emphases and a discussion of plans to expand the Foundation's population programs based on current work".
  - Ford Foundation Support for the Arts in the United States, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 241)
    A working paper from the Ford Foundation. "A discussion of new emphases in the Foundation's arts program".
  - Four Minorities and the Ph.D., Ford Foundation Graduate Fellowships for Blacks, Chicanos, Puerto Ricans, and American Indians, 1973 October (Box 23, Folder 242)
  - The Ford Foundation: Management and Program Trends in the Fifties and Sixties, 1971 June (Box 23, Folder 243)
  - Ford Foundation Travel and Study Grants, 1964-1968, 1969 July (Box 23, Folder 244)
    Includes lists of fellows by program (Education and Research, Humanities and the Arts, National Affairs, Non-Program, International) and an index.
  - American Graduate Schools of Education: A View from Abroad, harry Judge, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 245)
  - Afro-American Studies, Nathan Huggins, 1985 July (Box 23, Folder 246)
  - The Art of Managing the Environment, 1974 September (Box 23, Folder 247)
  - Three Essays: Black Studies in the United Sates, Robert L. Harris, Jr.; Darlene Clark Hine; Nellie McKay, 1990 June (Box 23, Folder 248)
  - The Ford Foundation in the Philippines (Box 24, Folder 249)
    Pamphlet, circa 2000.
  - Divide and Conquer: Responsible Security for America's Poor, David T. Ellwood, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 250)
    Ford Foundation Project on Social Welfare and the American Future, Occasional Paper 1.
  - Black and Hispanic Art museums: A Vibrant Cultural Resources, by Azade Ardali, 1989 December (Box 24, Folder 251)
    A Report to the Ford Foundation.
  - Educating School Children in the Law, Alex Elson, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 252)
  - Ecology and Resource Development in Southeast Asia, Gordon Conway and Jeff Romm, 1973 August (Box 24, Folder 253)
  - Ford Foundation Building, New Delhi, India - Introduction by Douglas Ensminger, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 254)
    Includes architectural and interior photographs of the Ford Foundation's newly constructed field office in New Delhi, India.
  - Research Project on Survey and Documentation of Monuments in the Upper Mahanadi Valley, P.K. Mishra, Sambalpur University, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 255)
    Includes album of original 5x7 black and white photographs.
  - Western Intellectuals and South Asia: The Ford Foundation and Western Economists in India and Pakistan, 1950-1970 (Tentative Title), George Rosen, 1980s (Box 24, Folder 256)
    Manuscript draft.
  - The Political Economy of Education: A Bibliography of Ford Foundation Supported Publications, 1968-1980, 1981 April (Box 24, Folder 257)
  - Language and Development: A Retrospective Survey of Ford Foundation Language Projects, 1952-1974, Melvin J. Fox, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 258)
  - Language and Development: A Retrospective Survey of Ford Foundation Language Projects, 1952-1974: Case Studies, Melvin J. Fox, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 259)
  - Rethinking Life and Work: Toward a Better Future: A report to the Ford Foundation based on a collaborative research project with three corporations: Xerox Corporation, Tandem Computers, Corning Inc., Rhona Rapoport and Lotte Bailyn, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 260)
  - La Raza: Ford Foundation Assistance to Mexican Americans, 1970s (Box 25, Folder 261)
  - Perspectives on Partnerships: Corporate and community leaders speak out on a collaborative strategy to revitalize America's urban and rural communities, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 262)
  - The Law and the Lore of Endowment Funds, William Cary and Craig Bright, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 263)
    Report to the Ford Foundation. The Educational Endowment Series.
  - Managing Educational Endowments / Advisory Committee on Endowment Management, 1969-1972 (Box 25, Folder 264)
    Includes 1st and 2nd editions. Report to the Ford Foundation. The Educational Endowment Series.
  - Readings on Family Planning and Population Program Management: Background Papers for a Ford Foundation Meeting on Population, Elsinore, Denmark, 1972 June (Box 25, Folder 265)
  - Left-Handed Fastballers: Scouting and Training America's Grass-Roots Leaders, 1966-1977: A Report based on a study for the Ford Foundation, conducted by David Nevin, 1981 August (Box 25, Folder 266)
  - The Public Interest Law Firm: New Voices for New Constituencies, 1973 February (Box 25, Folder 267)
  - The Common Good: Social Welfare and the American Future: Policy Recommendations of the Executive Panel, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 268)
    Ford Foundation Project on Social Welfare and the American Future. Attachment to Ford Foundation grant PA859-106, CONTINUED SUPPORT OF THE PROJECT ON SOCIAL WELFARE AND THE AMERICAN FUTURE (08590106).
  - International Studies in Six European Countries: United Kingdom, France, Federal Republic of Germany, The Netherlands, Sweden, Italy, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 269)
  - Philanthropy for Social Change: Four decades of Ford Foundation grant making in Eastern Africa, Stacey Young, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 270)
  - A Consultation on Higher Education in Africa: A Report to the Ford Foundation and Rockefeller Foundation, Trevor Coombe, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 271)
  - An Inquiry into the uses of Instructional Technology, James Armsey and Norman Dahl, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 272)
    A Ford Foundation Report.
  - Language Development: Selected papers from a Ford Foundation conference [New York, April 1967] on the state of the art, 1968 October (Box 26, Folder 273)
  - The International Economic Order: A Report to the Ford Foundation, C. Fred Bergsten and John A. Mathieson, 1973 September (Box 26, Folder 274)
  - Racial Segregation: Two Policy Views, Gary Orfield and William L. Taylor, 1979 October (Box 26, Folder 275)
    Reports to the Ford Foundation.
  - Language in Education: Problems and Prospects in Research and Training, Melvin J. Fox and Betty Skolnick, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 276)
  - International Organizations and Law, 1990 September (Box 26, Folder 277)
  - Law and Justice, 1974 October (Box 26, Folder 278)
  - Globalization, Health Sector Reform, Gender and Reproductive Health, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 279)
    Report of the Globalization Committee, Reproductive Health Affinity Group
  - Quality Preschool Programs: A Long-term Social investment, David P. Weikart, 1989 June (Box 26, Folder 280)
    Ford Foundation Project on Social Welfare and the American Future, Occasional Paper 5.
  - Poor, Rural, and Southern - A Ford Foundation Report, 1978 December (Box 26, Folder 281)
  - The Ford Foundation's Neighborhood and Family Initiative: The Challenge of Sustainability: An Interim Report, Robert Chaskin, Selma Chipenda Dansokho, Mark Joseph, 1997 July (Box 26, Folder 282)
    A Chapin Hall Report, Chapin Hall Center for Children at the University of Chicago
  - The Ford Foundation's Neighborhood and Family Initiative: Toward a Model of Comprehensive, Neighborhood-Based Development, Robert Chaskin, 1992 April (Box 27, Folder 283)
  - The Ford Foundation's Neighborhood and Family Initiative: Building Collaboration: An Interim Report, Robert Chaskin, Renae Ogletree, 1993 April (Box 27, Folder 284)
  - Created Equal: A Report on Ford Foundation Women's Programs, 1986 October (Box 27, Folder 285)
  - Forestry for Sustainable Rural Development: A Review of Ford Foundation-supported Community Forestry Programs in Asia, 1998 March (Box 27, Folder 286)
  - Growth Rings: Communities and Trees: Lessons from the Ford Foundation Community-Based Forestry Demonstration Program, 2000-2005 (Box 27, Folder 287)
    Published by the Aspen Institute.
  - Staying Power: Using Technical Assistance and Peer Learning to Enhance Donor Investments: Lessons from the Ford Foundation Community-Based Forestry Demonstration Program, 2000-2005 (Box 27, Folder 288)
  - Improving Local Governance: A Scrapbook of Awards Programs Supported by the Ford Foundation, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 289)
  - Asian American Women: Issues, Concerns, and Responsive Human and Civil Rights Advocacy, by Lora Jo Foo, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 290)
  - A Place in the World: A Review of the Global Debate on Tenure Security, Lunn Ellsworth, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 291)
  - Diversity on the Farm: How traditional crops around the world help to feed us all, and why we should reward the people who grown them, by Charles C. Mann, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 292)
  - Deeper Roots: Strengthening Community Tenure Security and Community Livelihoods, by Lynn Ellsworth and Andy White, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 293)
  - Borrowed from the Future: Challenges and Guidelines for Community-Based Natural Resource Management, by Jason Clay, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 294)
  - At the Crossroads: A Study of Federal HIV/AIDS Advocacy, Derek Hodel, 2004 May (Box 27, Folder 295)
  - Close to Home: Case Studies of Human Rights Work in the United States, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 296)
  - Ford Foundation International Division, Quarterly Report, Fiscal Year 1971, Summary of Grants and Projects as of, 1971 September 30 (Box 28, Folder 297)
  - Ford Foundation International Division, Development Assistance, Completed Grants and Projects, 1951 October - 1968 September 30 (Box 28, Folder 298, 299, 300, 301)
  - Press Comment on the Ford Foundation proposal to the Federal Communications Commission for a Broadcasters'' Nonprofit Domestic Satellite Service, 1966 August (Box 28, Folder 302)
  - Directory - Foreign Area Fellows, 1952-1953, of the Joint Committee of the American Council of Learned Societies and the Social Science Research Council, 1962-1963 - Formerly administered by the Ford Foundation, 1952-1962, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 303)
  - Humanistic Education: An Interpretation, Elizabeth Leonie Simpson, with an Annotated Bibliography by Mary Anne Gary, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 304)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government [annual reports], 1986-1994 (Box 29, Folder 305)
    An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation, in collaboration with the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University.
  - Innovations in American Government [annual reports], 1995-2000 (Box 29, Folder 306)
  - Innovating America, Fred Jordan, 1990 July (Box 29, Folder 307)
    Innovations in State and Local Government: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation and the John F. Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University.
  - Hispanics: Challenges and Opportunities, 1984 June (Box 29, Folder 308)
    "A look at he demographic, economic, social and political situation of Hispanics in the United States today, and at the Ford Foundation's initiatives to address the needs and impact of this growing population". A working paper from the Ford Foundation.
  - Hispanic theater in the United States and Puerto Rico, by Joanne Pottlitzer, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 309)
  - Investing for Social Gain: Reflections on Two Decades of Program-Related Investments (PRIs), 1991 December (Box 29, Folder 310)
  - Reforming Welfare with Work, by Judith M. Gueron, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 311)
    Ford Foundation Project on Social Welfare and the American Future, Occasional Paper 2.
  - HIV/AIDS Roundtable, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 312)
    Organized by the Ford Foundation in collaboration with the Vietnam National AIDS Standing Bureau and with assistance from the Center for Educational Exchange with Vietnam, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam, January 15-16, 2001.
  - Perspectives on India's Development in the 1990s: Symposium Overview, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 313)
    A symposium: 28-29 January 1992, Nehru Memorial Museum Library, New Delhi.
  - Higher, Wider, Education: A Report on Open Learning, 1976 June (Box 29, Folder 314)
  - The Ford Foundation Good Neighbor Committee, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 315)
  - Dancing: A Ford Foundation Report, Elizabeth Kendall, 1983 December (Box 29, Folder 316)
  - Litigation on Behalf of Women: A Review for the Ford Foundation, by Margaret A. Berger, 1980 May (Box 29, Folder 317)
  - New Initiatives for Transfer Students: urban Community College Transfer Opportunities Program, edited by Networks, sponsored by the Ford Foundation, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 318)
    See also Ford Foundation grant PA82-948 (08200948), Research Foundation of the City University of New York (CUNY), FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF A NEW CURRICULUM IN AMERICAN SOCIAL HISTORY PRIMARILY FOR USE IN COMMUNITY COLLEGES & ADULT EDUCATION PROGRAM.
  - Toward a Strategy for urban integration: Lessons in School and Housing policy from Twelve Cities, by Gary Orfield, 1981 December (Box 30, Folder 319)
  - Women, Children, and Poverty in America, 1985 January (Box 30, Folder 320)
    A working paper from the Ford Foundation. "A look at the problems facing low-income families headed by women and at some current and planned Ford Foundation responses".
  - Work and Family Responsibilities: Achieving a Balance, 1989 March (Box 30, Folder 321)
  - Women's Studies: A Retrospective: A Report to the Ford Foundation, by Beverly Guy-Sheftall, with Susan Heath, 1955 June (Box 30, Folder 322)
  - Urban Extension: A Report on Experimental Programs Assisted by the Ford Foundation, 1966 October (Box 30, Folder 323)
  - The Ford Foundation Bulletin, New Delhi, India, Field Office, 1994-2004 (Box 30, Folder 324)
  - The Ford Foundation in Bangladesh, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 325)
  - The Ford Foundation in China, 1991-2000 (Box 30, Folder 326)
  - The Wealth of a Nation, 1959 June (Box 30, Folder 327)
  - The University and World Affairs: Report of the Committee on the university and World Affairs, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 328)
  - A Work Experiment: Six Americans in a Swedish Plant, Robert B. Goldman, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 329)
  - Women's Studies in the United States: A Report to the Ford Foundation, by Catherine R. Stimpson, with Nina Kressner Cobb, 1986 June (Box 30, Folder 330)
  - Women in the World: A Ford Foundation Position Paper, 1980 November (Box 30, Folder 331)
  - Seminar on the Development and organization of Vocational Training and Technical Education (VTTE), 1965 (Box 30, Folder 332)